<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kanali</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kanali</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 16:41:54 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>/docs/v2/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 16:41:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/v2/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The goal of this section is to provide an introduction to each of Kanali&amp;rsquo;s configurable resources. More in depth documentation for each resource can be found here.

The ApiProxy Resource This resource declaratively defines how your upstream services are reached. There are 3 main sections that can be configured for this resource.
source how your proxy will be accessible
target how your upstream service will be reached</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Error Codes</title>
      <link>/docs/v2/errorcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 16:41:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/v2/errorcodes/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you&amp;rsquo;re visiting this page, changes are that Kanali has given you a response similar to this one:
{ &amp;quot;status&amp;quot;: 404, &amp;quot;message&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;No ApiProxy resource was not found that matches the request.&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;code&amp;quot;: 0, &amp;quot;details&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;Visit https://kanali.io/docs/v2/errorcodes/#00 for more details.&amp;quot; }  As promised in that response, the table below contains detailed information about each unique error code.
Details 00 Status: 404
Message: No ApiProxy resource was not found that matches the request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>/docs/v2/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 16:41:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/v2/tools/</guid>
      <description>Kanalictl Kanalictl is a command line utility that provides tooling for Kanali.
Installation # replace &#39;darwin&#39; and &#39;amd64&#39; with your OS and ARCH $ curl -O https://s3.amazonaws.com/kanalictl/release/$(curl -s https://s3.amazonaws.com/kanalictl/release/latest.txt)/darwin/amd64/kanalictl $ chmod +x kanalictl $ sudo mv kanalictl /usr/local/bin/kanalictl $ kanalictl -h  Usage $ kanalictl -h cli interface for kanali Usage: kanalictl [command] Available Commands: apikey performs operations on API key resources version version  Commands apikey Description: Performs utility operations on ApiKey resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flags</title>
      <link>/docs/v2/flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 16:43:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/v2/flags/</guid>
      <description>Usage Each of the following flags can be set to a custom value. Values can also be set via environment variables and configuration files. The name of the corresponding environment variable is documented below. The order of precedence is as follows (each item has precedence over the item below it):
Flag Environment Variable Config file
To illustrate an example, let&amp;rsquo;s assume we have a config.toml with the following value:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plugins</title>
      <link>/docs/v2/plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 16:43:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/v2/plugins/</guid>
      <description>API Key This plugin performs API key validation for all requests matching a certain ApiProxy. The plugin will ensure that the course and fine grained permissions that are specified in the given ApiKeyBinding resource are enforced. For details on how to configure the ApiKeyBinding resource, read the corresponding documentation here.
Configuration  FieldTypeDescription bindingNamestringName of ApiKeyBinding resource, in the same namespace as the ApiProxy, to be used. 
Example  plugins: - name: apikey config: bindingName: my-binding JWT  coming soon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deployment</title>
      <link>/docs/v2/deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 16:41:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/v2/deployment/</guid>
      <description>Helm  This is the recommended deployment option.
 Helm is a package manager for Kubernetes. Helm makes it easy to deploy all the components of an application and its dependencies.
Kanali&amp;rsquo;s Helm chart can be found here. Before demonstrating how to use this chart, let&amp;rsquo;s bootstrap a local Kubernetes environment so that you can follow along.
# Start a local Kubernetes cluster. $ minikube start --kubernetes-version=v1.9.4 --feature-gates CustomResourceValidation=true # Update a potentially stale kubeconfig context.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>